>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我们跳到这个关键词
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's jump
into the this keyword, and
试着用代码来了解它
try to understand it a little
bit better through code.
让我们在此练习中编写一些代码。
Let's write some code in this exercise.
在此练习中，您将重构当前使用的某些代码
In this exercise you're gonna be
refactoring some code that currently uses
模块模式，而您将改为使用该名称空间模式
the module pattern, and you're gonna
instead make it use that namespace pattern
在对象上使用的方法以及
where you have methods on an object and
它们使用此关键字引用该对象上的数据属性。
they refer to the data properties on
that object using the this keyword.
因此，如果我们查看 ex.js ，您会注意到我们有模块定义。
So if we look at the ex.js you'll notice
that we have our module definition.
我们有这个 defineWorkshop() 函数，它是我们的工厂功能。
We've got this defineWorkshop() function,
which is our factory function.
它正在制作这个公共 API 对象，它有这些内部的东西，
It's producing this publicAPI object and
it has these internal things,
这些内部数据值，如 currentEnrollment 和 studentRecords。
these internal data values,
like currentEnrollment and studentRecords.
我们想做的是将 deepJS 定义为函数
What we wanna do is turn the deepJS
from being defined by a function to
定义为具有以下内容的对象字面值
being defined as an object
literal that has
引用 currentEnrollment 和 studentRecords的属性。
properties that reference
the currentEnrollment and studentRecords.
所有这些功能，而不是隐藏起来，都是公共的
And all of those functions, instead of
being hidden, they'll all be public
对该对象的方法以及它们都将引用此停止。
methods on that object and they'll
all make references with this stop.
请注意，此代码中存在许多位置。
A word of caution, that there
are a bunch of places within this code.
例如，我们在这里通过一个类似的回调。
For example, we pass in a callback
like this one right here.
我们将此回调传递到 .map。
We pass in this callback to .map.
当它是一个规律的词法函数时
When it’s a regular lexical function,
在模块模式中，没有任何问题。
the way it is in the module pattern,
no problem whatsoever.
但当我们把它当功能的时候
But when we pass in this
to where functions,
我们有这个束缚的问题
we have the problem of our this binding.
所以你要小心注意你需要的地方
So you need to make sure to watch out for
the places where you need
把这些方法硬的引用了好吗
to pass in hard-bound references
to the methods, okay?
所以我的自述文件会给你关于
So the readme will give you
the instructions on taking out
defineWorkshop() 工厂，将其替换为对象。
the defineWorkshop() factory,
replacing it with an object.
更改所有内部引用和
Change all those internal references and
确保在需要时使用绑定，但不使用绑定
make sure that you use the bind where
it's needed, but don't use the bind on
所有功能调用都不需要它。
everything because it's not needed for
all of the function calls.
一如既往如果你被困住需要帮助
As always, if you get stuck and
need some help,
请确保查看解决方案文件 ( ex.fixfix) 。
make sure to look at the solution file,
the ex.fixed.
我们几分钟后就能通过解决方案
We'll be back in a few minutes
to talk through the solution.